dxpnet.com 2015-06-01

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Effective as of March, 7, 2008

This privacy statement covers the Web site located at http://www.dxpnet.com. The following topics are covered within this statement. For further information on DXP Publishing, INC or its privacy protections, contact the site administrator at staff@dxpnet.com.

  * What personally identifiable information DXP Publishing, INC collects.
  * What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  * What organization collects the information.
  * How DXP Publishing, INC uses the information.
  * With whom DXP Publishing, INC may share user information.
  * What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under DXP Publishing, INC control.
  * How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection and Use

Information Collection

DXP Publishing, INC is the sole owner of the information collected on www.dxpnet.com. DXP Publishing, INC collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Registration

In order to use some features of this Web site, a user must first become a member. During membership registration a user is required to give personal contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site and organization activities.

Information Use

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on our site, users who have registered as members would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a registered member rejects the cookie, they may still use the publicly available sections of the site.

Log Files

Like most standard Web sites DXP Publishing, INC creates server log files. Data in log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.

Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our online newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

Membership Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

Sharing

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties. At times DXP Publishing, INC makes use of third party vendors to provide services such as credit card transaction clearing, etc. These vendors operate exclusively under our direction and may not use any personal information for their own uses.

Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, DXP Publishing, INC, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Security

This Web site takes precautions to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done online at the member information page or by emailing our site director at staff@dxpnet.com. Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

Notification of Changes

f we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

DXP Publishing, INC

Phone: (877) 679-9520

Email: staff@dxpnet.com

PO BOX 154

Columbus, NE 68602
